<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>off-the-chains on Hobo Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/categories/off-the-chains/</link><description>Recent content in off-the-chains on Hobo Disc Golf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/categories/off-the-chains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Off the Chains: 04</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-04/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;What would you say your favorite course in Northern California is?&amp;rdquo;
Chains McGraw: &amp;ldquo;Now that&amp;rsquo;s a good question. So many to choose from throughout the years. That&amp;rsquo;s pretty tough, but put to it, I&amp;rsquo;d have to go with Brooktrails in Willits. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to put into words just how beautiful that place is. It&amp;rsquo;s a disc golf course nestled deep in the heart of Northern California, surrounded by towering redwoods and verdant greenery as far as the eye can see.</description></item><item><title>Off the Chains: 03</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-03/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-03/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Is there any one particular adventure that sticks out to you?&amp;rdquo;
Chains McGraw: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been on many wild disc golf adventures in my time, that&amp;rsquo;s for sure. Hmmmmmmmm&amp;hellip; Let me tell you about the time I played a round with a group of eccentric hippies deep in the heart of the California redwoods&amp;hellip;
Picture it, my friend. The summer of &amp;lsquo;78, a time when rebellion ran through the veins and the call of the open road echoed in our hearts.</description></item><item><title>Off the Chains: 02</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-02/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ve done a lot of traveling, especiall across the west. Given the company you keep and lifestyle you have had, we were wondering if you ever came across Hunter Thompson back in those days?&amp;rdquo;
Chains McGraw: &amp;ldquo;Ah, yes, Dr. Gonzo, what a character he was. Let me take you back to the &amp;rsquo;80s, a time of wild debauchery and even wilder disc golfing adventures. Hunter and I found ourselves on a road trip through the Pacific Northwest, chasing the elusive ace and living life to the fullest.</description></item><item><title>Off the Chains: 05</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 12:10:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-05/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;So, going back to that road trip in &amp;lsquo;76 in the Rockies, where did you end up after that?&amp;rdquo;
Chains McGraw: &amp;ldquo;Well, let&amp;rsquo;s see, it was the summer of &amp;lsquo;76, so that&amp;rsquo;s when I had come down off the mountain and ended up finding an unknown road that followed the Snake River. I found myself deep in the heart of Idaho with nothing but a map and a bag full of discs.</description></item><item><title>Off the Chains: 01</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-01/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Can you tell us about one of your earliest disc golf road trips?&amp;rdquo;
Chains McGraw: &amp;ldquo;Ah, yes. The disc golf road trip. A quintessential American adventure, fueled by adrenaline, questionable substances, and the unyielding thirst for the perfect round. I remember one particular journey, back in &amp;lsquo;76.
I had heard whispers of a course in the wilds of Montana, nestled in the bosom of the Rocky Mountains. A course like no other, they said.</description></item></channel></rss>