<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>courses on Hobo Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/tags/courses/</link><description>Recent content in courses on Hobo Disc Golf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/tags/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Northern California Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/northern-california-disc-golf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/northern-california-disc-golf/</guid><description>As Hunter S. Thompson once said, &amp;ldquo;Good people drink good beer.&amp;rdquo; And in Northern California, good people also play good disc golf.
The disc golf courses of Northern California are an absolute treasure that few people outside of the sport truly appreciate. From the towering redwoods of Brooktrails to the stunning vistas on Zephyr Cove of Lake Tahoe and the Sierra Nevada mountains (yes, techincally it&amp;rsquo;s in Nevada, but ya know), these courses offer an unparalleled experience of technical golf in the most stunning of settings.</description></item><item><title>Get Up and Go</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/get-up-and-go/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 09:02:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/get-up-and-go/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re new to disc golf and looking for beginner-friendly courses to hone your skills, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered! Disc golf is a fun and exciting sport that combines the joys of golf, the thrill of frisbee and beauty and serenity of hiking. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re in California or beyond, these courses offer a mix of open and wooded holes, well-maintained fairways, and moderate challenges that are perfect for beginners. So grab your discs and get ready to hit the courses!</description></item><item><title>Panning for Gold Courses</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/panning-for-gold-courses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 12:16:14 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/panning-for-gold-courses/</guid><description>Northern California&amp;rsquo;s gold country is not only full of rugged and significant history and stunning landscapes, but also hidden gem disc golf courses tucked away amidst the Sierra Nevada foothills. These courses offer a treasure trove of challenges and scenic beauty for avid disc golfers. Here are five disc golf courses in Northern California that are waiting to be discovered, each with its unique charm and allure.
Hogan&amp;rsquo;s Dam Disc Golf Course Nestled in Valley Springs, Hogan&amp;rsquo;s Dam Disc Golf Course is a true gem that offers a challenging and picturesque disc golfing experience.</description></item></channel></rss>