<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nomad on Hobo Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/tags/nomad/</link><description>Recent content in nomad on Hobo Disc Golf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:03:12 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/tags/nomad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Joe's Travels: 02</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:03:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-02/</guid><description>Hitting the Road As Hobo Joe set out on his latest road trip, he felt the familiar tingle of excitement and anticipation coursing through his veins. He started off the week in the South Bay, resting up after a busy couple weeks of disc golf, but soon found himself heading north to the quaint college town of Chico California.
It was there that he reunited with his longtime friend and the owner/operator of Jimbo&amp;rsquo;s Print Disc Golf Bag Tags, Jim.</description></item><item><title>Joe's Travels: 01</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-01/</guid><description>As the sun slowly rose over Tulloch Lake in Jamestown, California, Hobo Joe &amp;ldquo;Chains&amp;rdquo; McGraw opened his eyes, greeted by the breathtaking view of the still waters reflecting the morning sky. The first rays of the day illuminated the surrounding hills, signaling the arrival of spring with its warm embrace and colorful display of wildflowers. Joe knew he was in for a treat, both on and off the disc golf course, as he continued his journey through the Golden State.</description></item><item><title>Meet Hobo Joe</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/meet-hobo-joe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/meet-hobo-joe/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Hobo&amp;rdquo; Joe &amp;ldquo;Chains&amp;rdquo; McGraw was born in the rugged terrain of the Uinta Mountains, near Weber City Utah, where his kin attempted to make a living off the land. However, Joe&amp;rsquo;s restless spirit could not be contained in one place for long, and he soon set his sights on California. After a long and arduous journey, he found himself in the mountains of gold country, where he discovered his love for life on the road.</description></item><item><title>Why Go Nomad?</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/why-go-nomad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 21:12:59 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/why-go-nomad/</guid><description>Disc golf, a sport that captivates with its beauty and majesty, takes you on a journey through the wilderness, up the mountains, and into the heart of nature. It&amp;rsquo;s like hiking with a purpose, a purpose to conquer the fairway and reach the basket in as few throws as possible. As you stand at the tee pad, surrounded by the thick woods and rocky hillsides, the wilderness beckons, and you feel a sense of adventure coursing through your veins.</description></item></channel></rss>