<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hobo-dg on Hobo Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/tags/hobo-dg/</link><description>Recent content in hobo-dg on Hobo Disc Golf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/tags/hobo-dg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Off the Chains: 03</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-03/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-03/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Is there any one particular adventure that sticks out to you?&amp;rdquo;
Chains McGraw: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been on many wild disc golf adventures in my time, that&amp;rsquo;s for sure. Hmmmmmmmm&amp;hellip; Let me tell you about the time I played a round with a group of eccentric hippies deep in the heart of the California redwoods&amp;hellip;
Picture it, my friend. The summer of &amp;lsquo;78, a time when rebellion ran through the veins and the call of the open road echoed in our hearts.</description></item><item><title>Northern California Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/northern-california-disc-golf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/northern-california-disc-golf/</guid><description>As Hunter S. Thompson once said, &amp;ldquo;Good people drink good beer.&amp;rdquo; And in Northern California, good people also play good disc golf.
The disc golf courses of Northern California are an absolute treasure that few people outside of the sport truly appreciate. From the towering redwoods of Brooktrails to the stunning vistas on Zephyr Cove of Lake Tahoe and the Sierra Nevada mountains (yes, techincally it&amp;rsquo;s in Nevada, but ya know), these courses offer an unparalleled experience of technical golf in the most stunning of settings.</description></item><item><title>Disc Golf Is Life</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/disc-golf-is-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:05:55 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/disc-golf-is-life/</guid><description>Disc golf, my wild and untamed companion, is a symphony of flight that leaves the soul soaring through the air. It&amp;rsquo;s a dance between man and nature, where plastic discs become vessels of liberation, and fairways turn into portals to untamed adventures. The beauty of disc golf lies not only in the graceful arcs and spins of the flying disc but in the essence of the hobo lifestyle it embodies.</description></item><item><title>Off the Chains: 02</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-02/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ve done a lot of traveling, especiall across the west. Given the company you keep and lifestyle you have had, we were wondering if you ever came across Hunter Thompson back in those days?&amp;rdquo;
Chains McGraw: &amp;ldquo;Ah, yes, Dr. Gonzo, what a character he was. Let me take you back to the &amp;rsquo;80s, a time of wild debauchery and even wilder disc golfing adventures. Hunter and I found ourselves on a road trip through the Pacific Northwest, chasing the elusive ace and living life to the fullest.</description></item><item><title>Off the Chains: 01</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-01/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Can you tell us about one of your earliest disc golf road trips?&amp;rdquo;
Chains McGraw: &amp;ldquo;Ah, yes. The disc golf road trip. A quintessential American adventure, fueled by adrenaline, questionable substances, and the unyielding thirst for the perfect round. I remember one particular journey, back in &amp;lsquo;76.
I had heard whispers of a course in the wilds of Montana, nestled in the bosom of the Rocky Mountains. A course like no other, they said.</description></item><item><title>Hobo Disc Golf Bag Tags</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/bagtags/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/bagtags/</guid><description>What are Hobo Disc Golf Bag Tags? At least once a year, Hobo Disc Golf will sponsor a local tournament to initially seed and handout tags in-person as a community. This year we are sponsoring the AM Rush Tournament on June 17th and 18th 2023. Be sure to register today! However, if you are not able to make it to the tournament(s) for some reason (but what could be more important, really?</description></item><item><title>Inagural Hobo DG Bag Tag Event 2023</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/special-bag-tag-event-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/special-bag-tag-event-2023/</guid><description>Hobo Disc Golf Bag Tags! Join us June 17th and 18th in Grass Valley at the Lost Lake Disc Golf Course for the AM Rush Tournament which will also include the inagural Hobo Disc Golf Bag Tag kick-off!
At least once a year, Hobo Disc Golf will sponsor a local tournament to initially seed and handout tags in-person as a community. However, if you are not able to make the tournament(s) for some reason (but what could be more important, really?</description></item><item><title>Joe's Travels: 02</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:03:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-02/</guid><description>Hitting the Road As Hobo Joe set out on his latest road trip, he felt the familiar tingle of excitement and anticipation coursing through his veins. He started off the week in the South Bay, resting up after a busy couple weeks of disc golf, but soon found himself heading north to the quaint college town of Chico California.
It was there that he reunited with his longtime friend and the owner/operator of Jimbo&amp;rsquo;s Print Disc Golf Bag Tags, Jim.</description></item><item><title>Joe's Travels: 01</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-01/</guid><description>As the sun slowly rose over Tulloch Lake in Jamestown, California, Hobo Joe &amp;ldquo;Chains&amp;rdquo; McGraw opened his eyes, greeted by the breathtaking view of the still waters reflecting the morning sky. The first rays of the day illuminated the surrounding hills, signaling the arrival of spring with its warm embrace and colorful display of wildflowers. Joe knew he was in for a treat, both on and off the disc golf course, as he continued his journey through the Golden State.</description></item><item><title>Meet Hobo Joe</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/meet-hobo-joe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/meet-hobo-joe/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Hobo&amp;rdquo; Joe &amp;ldquo;Chains&amp;rdquo; McGraw was born in the rugged terrain of the Uinta Mountains, near Weber City Utah, where his kin attempted to make a living off the land. However, Joe&amp;rsquo;s restless spirit could not be contained in one place for long, and he soon set his sights on California. After a long and arduous journey, he found himself in the mountains of gold country, where he discovered his love for life on the road.</description></item><item><title>Why Go Nomad?</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/why-go-nomad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 21:12:59 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/why-go-nomad/</guid><description>Disc golf, a sport that captivates with its beauty and majesty, takes you on a journey through the wilderness, up the mountains, and into the heart of nature. It&amp;rsquo;s like hiking with a purpose, a purpose to conquer the fairway and reach the basket in as few throws as possible. As you stand at the tee pad, surrounded by the thick woods and rocky hillsides, the wilderness beckons, and you feel a sense of adventure coursing through your veins.</description></item></channel></rss>