<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>norcal on Hobo Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/tags/norcal/</link><description>Recent content in norcal on Hobo Disc Golf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/tags/norcal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Inagural Hobo DG Bag Tag Event 2023</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/special-bag-tag-event-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/special-bag-tag-event-2023/</guid><description>Hobo Disc Golf Bag Tags! Join us June 17th and 18th in Grass Valley at the Lost Lake Disc Golf Course for the AM Rush Tournament which will also include the inagural Hobo Disc Golf Bag Tag kick-off!
At least once a year, Hobo Disc Golf will sponsor a local tournament to initially seed and handout tags in-person as a community. However, if you are not able to make the tournament(s) for some reason (but what could be more important, really?</description></item><item><title>Joe's Travels: 02</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:03:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-02/</guid><description>Hitting the Road As Hobo Joe set out on his latest road trip, he felt the familiar tingle of excitement and anticipation coursing through his veins. He started off the week in the South Bay, resting up after a busy couple weeks of disc golf, but soon found himself heading north to the quaint college town of Chico California.
It was there that he reunited with his longtime friend and the owner/operator of Jimbo&amp;rsquo;s Print Disc Golf Bag Tags, Jim.</description></item><item><title>Joe's Travels: 01</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-01/</guid><description>As the sun slowly rose over Tulloch Lake in Jamestown, California, Hobo Joe &amp;ldquo;Chains&amp;rdquo; McGraw opened his eyes, greeted by the breathtaking view of the still waters reflecting the morning sky. The first rays of the day illuminated the surrounding hills, signaling the arrival of spring with its warm embrace and colorful display of wildflowers. Joe knew he was in for a treat, both on and off the disc golf course, as he continued his journey through the Golden State.</description></item><item><title>Panning for Gold Courses</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/panning-for-gold-courses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 12:16:14 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/panning-for-gold-courses/</guid><description>Northern California&amp;rsquo;s gold country is not only full of rugged and significant history and stunning landscapes, but also hidden gem disc golf courses tucked away amidst the Sierra Nevada foothills. These courses offer a treasure trove of challenges and scenic beauty for avid disc golfers. Here are five disc golf courses in Northern California that are waiting to be discovered, each with its unique charm and allure.
Hogan&amp;rsquo;s Dam Disc Golf Course Nestled in Valley Springs, Hogan&amp;rsquo;s Dam Disc Golf Course is a true gem that offers a challenging and picturesque disc golfing experience.</description></item></channel></rss>