<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Hobo Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Hobo Disc Golf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 21:12:59 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Go Nomad?</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/why-go-nomad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 21:12:59 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/why-go-nomad/</guid><description>Disc golf, a sport that captivates with its beauty and majesty, takes you on a journey through the wilderness, up the mountains, and into the heart of nature. It&amp;rsquo;s like hiking with a purpose, a purpose to conquer the fairway and reach the basket in as few throws as possible. As you stand at the tee pad, surrounded by the thick woods and rocky hillsides, the wilderness beckons, and you feel a sense of adventure coursing through your veins.</description></item><item><title>Get Up and Go</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/get-up-and-go/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 09:02:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/get-up-and-go/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re new to disc golf and looking for beginner-friendly courses to hone your skills, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered! Disc golf is a fun and exciting sport that combines the joys of golf, the thrill of frisbee and beauty and serenity of hiking. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re in California or beyond, these courses offer a mix of open and wooded holes, well-maintained fairways, and moderate challenges that are perfect for beginners. So grab your discs and get ready to hit the courses!</description></item><item><title>Panning for Gold Courses</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/panning-for-gold-courses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 12:16:14 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/panning-for-gold-courses/</guid><description>Northern California&amp;rsquo;s gold country is not only full of rugged and significant history and stunning landscapes, but also hidden gem disc golf courses tucked away amidst the Sierra Nevada foothills. These courses offer a treasure trove of challenges and scenic beauty for avid disc golfers. Here are five disc golf courses in Northern California that are waiting to be discovered, each with its unique charm and allure.
Hogan&amp;rsquo;s Dam Disc Golf Course Nestled in Valley Springs, Hogan&amp;rsquo;s Dam Disc Golf Course is a true gem that offers a challenging and picturesque disc golfing experience.</description></item></channel></rss>