<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Hobo Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Hobo Disc Golf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Off the Chains: 01</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/off-the-chains-01/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Can you tell us about one of your earliest disc golf road trips?&amp;rdquo;
Chains McGraw: &amp;ldquo;Ah, yes. The disc golf road trip. A quintessential American adventure, fueled by adrenaline, questionable substances, and the unyielding thirst for the perfect round. I remember one particular journey, back in &amp;lsquo;76.
I had heard whispers of a course in the wilds of Montana, nestled in the bosom of the Rocky Mountains. A course like no other, they said.</description></item><item><title>Hobo DG Weekly: 01</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/weekly-newsletter-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/weekly-newsletter-01/</guid><description>Hobo DG Bag Tag Top 5 Tag Hobo 1 coming soon 2 coming soon 3 coming soon 4 coming soon 5 coming soon Hobo Disc Golf Bag Tag Kick-Off! Register for the AM Rush and kick-off the inagural Hobo DG Bag Tag event! Still Room Left TOURNEY HOBO DG EVENT? 2023 NADGT Exclusive @ Hanging Oaks N Auburn Open N 3rd Annual NorCal Am Jam N The Levi Memorial N AM Rush Y A look back at the Week This past week saw the ever-entertaining May the 4th come and go.</description></item><item><title>Inagural Hobo DG Bag Tag Event 2023</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/special-bag-tag-event-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/special-bag-tag-event-2023/</guid><description>Hobo Disc Golf Bag Tags! Join us June 17th and 18th in Grass Valley at the Lost Lake Disc Golf Course for the AM Rush Tournament which will also include the inagural Hobo Disc Golf Bag Tag kick-off!
At least once a year, Hobo Disc Golf will sponsor a local tournament to initially seed and handout tags in-person as a community. However, if you are not able to make the tournament(s) for some reason (but what could be more important, really?</description></item><item><title>Joe's Travels: 02</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:03:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-02/</guid><description>Hitting the Road As Hobo Joe set out on his latest road trip, he felt the familiar tingle of excitement and anticipation coursing through his veins. He started off the week in the South Bay, resting up after a busy couple weeks of disc golf, but soon found himself heading north to the quaint college town of Chico California.
It was there that he reunited with his longtime friend and the owner/operator of Jimbo&amp;rsquo;s Print Disc Golf Bag Tags, Jim.</description></item><item><title>Psychology of Disc Golf</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/psychology-of-disc-golf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 09:33:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/psychology-of-disc-golf/</guid><description>Disc golf is not just a physical sport but also a mental game. The psychology of disc golf is often overlooked, but it can play a significant role in one&amp;rsquo;s play. Many players face mental blocks and challenges that can hold them back from playing their best. However, with the right mindset, players can overcome these obstacles and improve their game.
One of the things that has helped me the most in many aspects of life, not just sports, in terms of mindset has been the philosophy of &amp;ldquo;Wei wu wei&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;Do without doing&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Joe's Travels: 01</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/joes-travels-01/</guid><description>As the sun slowly rose over Tulloch Lake in Jamestown, California, Hobo Joe &amp;ldquo;Chains&amp;rdquo; McGraw opened his eyes, greeted by the breathtaking view of the still waters reflecting the morning sky. The first rays of the day illuminated the surrounding hills, signaling the arrival of spring with its warm embrace and colorful display of wildflowers. Joe knew he was in for a treat, both on and off the disc golf course, as he continued his journey through the Golden State.</description></item><item><title>But Which Disc</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/but-which-disc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 08:19:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/but-which-disc/</guid><description>Disc golf is a sport that requires skill, strategy, and the right equipment. The most important piece of equipment is, of course, the disc. There are three types of discs: drivers, midranges, and putters, each with its own unique characteristics and purposes. Choosing the right disc can make all the difference in your game, so it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand what each disc is designed to do.
Drivers Drivers are designed for maximum distance and speed.</description></item><item><title>Meet Hobo Joe</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/meet-hobo-joe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/meet-hobo-joe/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Hobo&amp;rdquo; Joe &amp;ldquo;Chains&amp;rdquo; McGraw was born in the rugged terrain of the Uinta Mountains, near Weber City Utah, where his kin attempted to make a living off the land. However, Joe&amp;rsquo;s restless spirit could not be contained in one place for long, and he soon set his sights on California. After a long and arduous journey, he found himself in the mountains of gold country, where he discovered his love for life on the road.</description></item><item><title>Why Go Nomad?</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/why-go-nomad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 21:12:59 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/why-go-nomad/</guid><description>Disc golf, a sport that captivates with its beauty and majesty, takes you on a journey through the wilderness, up the mountains, and into the heart of nature. It&amp;rsquo;s like hiking with a purpose, a purpose to conquer the fairway and reach the basket in as few throws as possible. As you stand at the tee pad, surrounded by the thick woods and rocky hillsides, the wilderness beckons, and you feel a sense of adventure coursing through your veins.</description></item><item><title>Get Up and Go</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/get-up-and-go/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 09:02:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/get-up-and-go/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re new to disc golf and looking for beginner-friendly courses to hone your skills, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered! Disc golf is a fun and exciting sport that combines the joys of golf, the thrill of frisbee and beauty and serenity of hiking. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re in California or beyond, these courses offer a mix of open and wooded holes, well-maintained fairways, and moderate challenges that are perfect for beginners. So grab your discs and get ready to hit the courses!</description></item><item><title>Panning for Gold Courses</title><link>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/panning-for-gold-courses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 12:16:14 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.hobodiscgolf.com/posts/panning-for-gold-courses/</guid><description>Northern California&amp;rsquo;s gold country is not only full of rugged and significant history and stunning landscapes, but also hidden gem disc golf courses tucked away amidst the Sierra Nevada foothills. These courses offer a treasure trove of challenges and scenic beauty for avid disc golfers. Here are five disc golf courses in Northern California that are waiting to be discovered, each with its unique charm and allure.
Hogan&amp;rsquo;s Dam Disc Golf Course Nestled in Valley Springs, Hogan&amp;rsquo;s Dam Disc Golf Course is a true gem that offers a challenging and picturesque disc golfing experience.</description></item></channel></rss>